

Personal infoBorn in Terrassa on 03.02.1994

▶ bernatferrerm@gmail.com

* +34 601436012 +49 5770251085

★ Terrassa (Barcelona)

Languages

Catalan
Spanish
English
German

Programming Languages

Software tools, frameworks

Git Linux Laravel React MongoDB Nodejs • • 0 0 Android 0 0 0 Figma 0 0 0 Tableau 000 Excel Krita • • • • Godot • • • • •

Soft Skills

- Logical mindset
- Hard working
- Empathic
- Open minded

Interests

- Software development
- Science
- Language learning
- Hiking







Bernat Ferrer

Backend developer

I am a 26 year old software developer, opened to new experiences and projects as well as curious about several areas of the knowledge. I am really motivated in the area of software development, constantly striving to learn more and excel. I am always engaged in personal software projects.

Professional experience

Fullstack developer at Assembler, Barcelona. June 2020-Now

Working with the programming languages HTML,CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL and the frameworks Laravel, Nodejs and React. Some of the projects are listed below.

- Development of a social network with PHP using the Laravel with the main features of a social network (comments, likes, following, notifications). Implementation of a relational database using SQL and database migrations. Usage of MVC pattern with object oriented programming. repo link
- Development of a fully functional calendar with JavaScript, CSS and HTML and without the help of external libraries. try it here
- Development of a file-system manager with JavaScript, HTML and PHP. repo link

Android developer as a freelance, Barcelona. March 2020-May 2020

Development of an app for language learning using Kotlin and the MVVM pattern. Published in the google play platform App link.

Data analyst at M-net, Munich. Sept 2018 - Oct 2019

Analysis of revenue data using Tableau and Excel in order to optimize benefits and reduce lo-

Physics Researcher at the USM, Munich. 2018 - 2019

Development of an interface for the visualization of data coming from astrophysical simulations of protoplanetary disks. Name of the master thesis: *Constraints in gap opening timescales in the HD 623296 protoplanetary disk*.

Private maths teacher

Maths lessons for high-school students, Terrassa. 2012-2016.

Education

Master in software development Assembler School, Barcelona. 2020-Now

Astrophysics Master Ludwig Maximilians University, Munich (LMU). 2017-2019

Physics Degree Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona (UAB). 2012-2017

Additionally

A user experience course at LMU, Munich. 2019.

A six month internship at the European southern observatory (ESO), Munich. April -Sept 2018.

Volunteer in a homeless shelter in the city of Pittsburgh, USA. Summer 2013.